counterpunch.org 2019-08-24

# Privacy Policy - CounterPunch.org

Welcome to CounterPunch’s Online Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”). This Privacy Policy describes the type of information CounterPunch collects. First and foremost, we DO NOT share your information with any third parties, we do not run advertisements, nor do we permanently store information on your visits to our site. However, we do utilize cookies (see below) for ongoing website functionality.

By using CounterPunch you agree to this Privacy Policy and you give us your “opt-in” consent to allow us to utilize cookies. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not visit or utilize CounterPunch. This is in accordance with the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation.

Additionally, for data stored on our CounterPunch Store, please visit our store’s privacy page. Also, if you agree to sign up for our newsletter email, we will store only the information provided and will never share your email address or other information provided with any third party or advertiser.

Counterpunch does not sell advertising, which means we only use cookies to understand the basic patterns of our readers. CounterPunch uses analytics and performance cookies to collect information about website traffic and how users interact with CounterPunch. The information collected includes the number of visitors, the websites that referred visitors to CounterPunch, the pages visited, what time of day they visited, whether they have visited CounterPunch before, and other similar information. We use this data to help operate CounterPunch more efficiently and improve user experience. This cookie data is never shared with any third parties.
